{
    "id": "aa49c23546e54153a758c4d85f087671",
    "title": "Few, little | grammar exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "fa3a0cc36a684c9f98a05e413ac4a20f",
            "title": "Few And Little",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "………………….. people can keep a secret.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Few",
                        "The few",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "………………. grain that we had was damaged in the rain.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Little",
                        "The little"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She showed …………………. any remorse.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "hardly",
                        "hard"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He spent ………………… . days that were left to him in solitude and meditation.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "few",
                        "a few",
                        "the few"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "………………… Jews that live in Kochi have assimilated themselves into the local culture.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Few",
                        "A few",
                        "The few"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "We met ……………… Germans during our vacation in Italy.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "few",
                        "a few",
                        "the few"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "In ……………… words he expressed his gratitude.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "few",
                        "a few",
                        "the few"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "……………….. remarks that he made were very provocative.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Few",
                        "A few",
                        "The few"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "…………………. friends that she has are influential people.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Few",
                        "A few",
                        "The few"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "………………… did he realize what he was getting himself into.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Little",
                        "A little",
                        "The little"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}